[
    {
        "id": 1061,
        "question": "Which of the following are true for Controllers in Laravel?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "You should avoid using controllers as it is considered bad practice.",
            "answer_b": "Controllers are stored in the app/Http/Controllers directory.",
            "answer_c": "Controllers can group related request handling logic into a single class.",
            "answer_d": "A controller is the \"C\" in the \"MVC\" (Model-View-Controller) architecture, which is what Laravel is based on.",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    },
    {
        "id": 1058,
        "question": "What is Laravel?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Laravel is an open-source widely used PHP framework.",
            "answer_b": "Laravel is an open-source widely used JavaScript framework.",
            "answer_c": "Laravel is an open-source widely used Python framework.",
            "answer_d": "Laravel is an open-source widely used Ruby framework.",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 1062,
        "question": "Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Controller?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "php artisan make:controller controller_name",
            "answer_b": "php artisan create:controller controller_name",
            "answer_c": "php artisan controller create controller_name",
            "answer_d": "php artisan controller:make controller_name",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 1064,
        "question": "Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Model?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "php artisan create:model ModelName",
            "answer_b": "php artisan model:make ModelName",
            "answer_c": "php artisan model create ModelName",
            "answer_d": "php artisan make:model ModelName",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_d"
    }, {
        "id": 1063,
        "question": "What is service container in Laravel?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Service container is a tool used for performing dependency injection in Laravel.",
            "answer_b": "Dockerized Laravel applications are called service containers.",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 1065,
        "question": "What is the name of the Template Engine utilized by Laravel?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Blade",
            "answer_b": "Twig",
            "answer_c": "Pug",
            "answer_d": "Squirrelly",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 1059,
        "question": "What is HTTP middleware in Laravel?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "HTTP middleware is a technique for installing Laravel via HTTP.",
            "answer_b": "HTTP middleware is a technique for filtering HTTP requests.",
            "answer_c": "HTTP middleware is a technique for updating Laravel via HTTP.",
            "answer_d": "HTTP middleware is a web server used by Laravel similar to Apache and Nginx.",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 1067,
        "question": "Which artisan command will you used to enable maintenance mode in Laravel?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "php artisan maintenance",
            "answer_b": "php artisan down",
            "answer_c": "php artisan stop",
            "answer_d": "php artisan pause",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 1060,
        "question": "Which of the following are true for routes in Laravel?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "You can not pass any arguments to your routes.",
            "answer_b": "Routes can point to a method on a controller and also dictate which HTTP methods are able to hit that URI.",
            "answer_c": "A route is an endpoint specified by a URI (Uniform Resource Identifier).",
            "answer_d": "Routes can only handle GET requests",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 1066,
        "question": "Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Migration?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "php artisan make:migrations create_users_table",
            "answer_b": "php artisan create:migrations create_users_table",
            "answer_c": "php artisan make:migration create_users_table",
            "answer_d": "php artisan make:migrations create_users_table",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Laravel"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    }
]
